Come in Dean. please sit down.
进来 Dean. 请坐下.
Thanks.
谢谢
Now we can go over your job description.
现在咱们可以  过一下你的工作描述了.
Sure.
好的.
Can you use a word processor, Dean?
你能用文字处理软件吗, Dean?
Yes, I can.
是, 我能.
Other computer programs?
其他的电脑程序呢?
Databases? Spreadsheets?
数据库? 电子表格?
I can work with computers very well.
我能很好地用电脑工作
Good.
好
Can you speak any foreign languages?
你能够讲任何外语吗?
Not really. I speak a little Spanish,
几乎不能. 我讲一点西班牙语,
but I can't understand a word.
但我听不懂一个词.
I see.
我明白了.
Well, you can't translate Spanish for us.
Well,你不能翻译西班牙语  为我们.
But maybe you can help us understand our computers.
但或许你可以帮助我们  搞懂我们的电脑.
I can do that.
我可以做那个.
All right, Dean. Talk to William at the front desk.
好的, Dean. 和William聊聊  在前台.
You can work with him today.
你可以跟他一起工作  今天.
Great.
很好
You can find your way, can't you?
你能找到你的路, 不能吗?
Sure.
可以的.
Good luck. And welcome to the team.
好运. 并且欢迎来到团队
Thanks.
谢谢